♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 5=
You cheated and stopped touching me.
Your ego couldn't handle it.
Some darkness
has to be faced alone.
No. I've been trying to work through it.
You're the one acting out of spite.
And you slept with another man!
And your way of working through it
was to cheat?
Do you have to act morally superior?
I'm a man.
Knowing my girlfriend
had a past like that,
was I wrong to struggle to accept it?
Huh?
I mean,
I forgave you.
Why can't you forgive me?
My past
doesn't need your forgiveness.
Su Yan.
What makes you so superior?
You don't need anyone's forgiveness.
You again.
Cheng Lin.
I looked you up.
You've only been out of juvie
for two months.
Right?
What are you after?
Her money?
I'll pay you.
Is that enough?
How about now?
- Duan Cizhou, you...
- Take it.
Take it all!
Get lost!
Let her go!
You let go!
Both of you, let go of me!
Su Yan.
I...
Why are you following me?
Didn't he give you money?
Can you just leave me alone?
Men are all jerks.
Let go of me.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Why did you come back?
I know you love ice cream.
So I bought a bunch of flavors.
For you.
Su Yan.
Tell me.
What would make you feel better?
Kiss me.
You're up.
I made breakfast.
You cleaned all this up?
Yeah.
What time did you get up?
Six.
I always wake up at six.
A habit I picked up in juvie.
Drink some water first.
It's warm.
Are you a neat freak?
A little.
But you can make a mess.
I'll clean it up.
Eat something first.
I just made wontons. Try some.
This is so good.
I used to make them for my mom.
From now on, I can...
What are your plans?
School?
Or do you want to learn a trade?
I can help with either.
Try this.
A soft-boiled egg.
Don't change the subject.
I'm not changing the subject.
Before I got out,
I had a lot of things in mind.
Take it.
Take your time figuring it out.
I can afford to support you.
A man can support the woman he loves.
So why can't a woman do the same?
(Support the man she likes.)
(She said she likes me.)
(No, no.)
I-I don't need this.
I can take care of myself.
From now on,
I'll work hard
to be good enough for you.
So you're really into that cute kid?
No.
A nineteen-year-old boy
falling for a mature, confident woman?
Perfectly normal.
Spend money on him if you want.
Enjoy the eye candy.
Just don't catch feelings.
I won't.
He's like this ice cream.
Sweet.
Refreshing.
Perfect for cooling me off.
But I won't overindulge.
I used to
give others 80% of my love
and keep only 20% for myself.
But now,
I want to keep 80% for myself.
Okay.
=The One=
She's recovering well.
She should be discharged soon.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll get back to work.
I used to
give others 80% of my love
and keep only 20% for myself.
But now,
I want to keep 80% for myself.
(But if I love,
I love with everything I have.)
(And I expect the same.)
(Su Yan.)
(Tell me.)
(What would make you feel better?)
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
♪Memories pile up, moment by moment♪
♪One careless word brings my walls down♪
♪I escape the past, then fall back in♪
♪Longing twists into a hopeless knot♪
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
♪I hum this song alone♪
♪Counting every fleeting moment♪
♪Every corner still reminds me of you♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪